all right houses welcome back and in this video I'm going to talk to you
没事 的房屋迎回 和 这个视频我要和你谈谈
about the map function in Python so the map function is basically a way that you
关于地图功能在Python 所以 map函数基本上 就是你的一种方式
can take a list whatever it is you know a list of foods of names of numbers and you can run each item in that list
无论 你知道 什么 ， 都可以列出清单 数字和名称的食物清单 您 可以运行该列表中的每个项目
through a function really easily so let's go ahead and make a simple list
通过一个功能真的很容易 让我们继续 做一个简单的清单
I'll just say income so this list is how much money I make and I'll say the first week of work I made $10 the second week
我只会说收入所以这个清单就是 这样的 我赚了很多钱， 我会说第一个 工作周我第二周赚了10美元
I made 30 bucks and the last week I made 75 bucks
我赚了30块钱，上周我做了 75块钱
all right so now I have a list of stuff but I also have this function and I'm just going to make this function really
好的，所以现在我有一份东西清单 但我也有这个功能，我 只会 让这个功能真的
simple to demonstrate you know because we aren't really learning about functions or anything complex I just
简单地证明你知道因为 我们并没有真正了解 功能或任何复杂的我 只是
want to demonstrate the map function so all this function is going to do is it's
要演示地图功能，所以 这个功能将要做的就是它
going to take each of these items in multiplying by two so double your money
要把这些物品拿走 乘以2可以 使你的钱增加一倍
so we're going to pass in dollars which is each item in the list and we're just
所以我们要传递美元 在 列表中的每个项目，我们只是
going to return okay there we go returned dollars multiplied by two
要恢复 还好吧，我们去 返还美元 乘以 2
all right so what we can do is we can make a for loop so for items in income and then we can do this yadda yadda
没事 所以我们可以做的是，我们可以 为 收入 项目制作一个for循环 然后我们可以做这个 yadda yadda
tomato tomahto but there's actually an easier and more efficient way so what we
番茄tomahto但实际上有 一个 更简单，更有效的方式， 所以我们
can do is actually call the map function now the map function takes two
可以做的其实就是调用map函数 现在map函数需要两个
parameters the first one is what function are you going to run all of
参数第 一个是什么 功能你打算全部运行
your items through well it's just double money now we don't have any parameters
通过它你的项目只是双倍 钱，现在我们没有任何参数
and the second function is alright what is the list that you want to iterate
第二个功能是 好的 是要 遍历列表
through well we only have one list which is this so do that
通过我们只有一个列表 是这样做的
so what this is going to do is it's going to go through this list and for
所以这是怎么回事呢 要通过这个列表和
each item 10 30 75 it's going to run it through this function now if we just run
每个项目10 30 75它将运行它 如果我们刚刚运行，现在通过这个功能
this right now it's not going to show anything because we don't have any output so let me just go ahead and
现在这不会显示出来 因为我们没有 任何东西 输出让我继续前进
very like new income equals list.map all right looking good
非常喜欢新收入等于list.map all 看起来不错
so I basically am going to run through this multiply each of these values by
所以我基本上要跑了 这将每个 值乘以
two so we end up with 20 60 and 150 and then I'm just going to take all those
两个，所以 我们最终得到 20 60和150和 然后我就要拿走所有这些
values and convert it to a list so we can print it out so print new income and
值并将其转换为列表，以便我们 可以打印出来，以便打印 新的收入 和
there you go so now you see 20 60 and 150 now again you can also do this with
你去， 所以现在你看到 20 60和 150 现在又 你 也可以做到这一点 与
a for loop so just say for item in income and then you can do it that way
一个for 循环 所以只说对于项目 收入，然后你可以这样做的
but this is a much easier way in my opinion and it's a lot more compact so
但这对我来说更容易 意见，而且它更紧凑
it doesn't clutter up all your code so there you go that is what map is
它不会使你的所有代码混乱 那你 去的地图是什么
basically taking some kind of iterable and are running it through a function
基本上采取某种 迭代 并通过一个函数运行它
boom roasted see you next time
热潮烤下次见